Guide to the Time Inc. Time Research Center Files: Subject Files MS 3009-RG 13.Series III
New-York Historical Society
- Series III. Subject Files, 1926-2000; 774 Linear feet (774 boxes)
  - Press: United States: Associations: D, 1948-1989 (Offsite-box 2181, Folder 36)
  - Press: United States: Associations: Detroit Newspaper Publishers Association, 1955-1964 (Offsite-box 2181, Folder 37)
  - Press: United States: Associations: Drama Desk, 1959-1993 (Offsite-box 2181, Folder 38)
  - Press: United States: Associations: E-G, 1948-1993 (Offsite-box 2181, Folder 39-41)
  - Press: United States: Associations: Gridiron, 1929-1992 (Offsite-box 2182, Folder 1-3)
  - Press: United States: Associations: H-I, 1935-1993 (Offsite-box 2182, Folder 4-5)
  - Press: United States: Associations: Inner Circle, 1954-1987 (Offsite-box 2182, Folder 6)
  - Press: United States: Associations: International Newspaper Promotion Association, 1959-1981 (Offsite-box 2182, Folder 7)
  - Press: United States: Associations: J, 1953-1975 (Offsite-box 2182, Folder 8)
  - Press: United States: Associations: Joint Board, 1964-1965 (Offsite-box 2182, Folder 9)
  - Press: United States: Associations: K-M, 1936-1993, undated (Offsite-box 2182, Folder 10-12)
  - Press: United States: Associations: Magazine Publishers of America, 1957-1993 (Offsite-box 2182, Folder 13-17)
  - Press: United States: Associations: Na-Nz, 1930-1993, undated (Offsite-box 2182, Folder 18-21)
  - Press: United States: Associations: National Association of Science Writers, 1953-1986 (Offsite-box 2182, Folder 22)
  - Press: United States: Associations: National Headliners Club, 155-1963 (Offsite-box 2182, Folder 23)
  - Press: United States: Associations: National News Council, 1963-1984 (Offsite-box 2182, Folder 24)
  - Press: United States: Associations: National Newspaper Association, 1951-1988 (Offsite-box 2182, Folder 25)
  - Press: United States: Associations: National Press Club, 1933-1993 (Offsite-box 2183, Folder 1-11)
  - Press: United States: Associations: New York Financial Writers Association, 1955-1979 (Offsite-box 2183, Folder 12-13)
  - Press: United States: Associations: New York Press Club, 1956-1984 (Offsite-box 2183, Folder 14)
  - Press: United States: Associations: New York State Publishers Association, 1948-1982 (Offsite-box 2183, Folder 15)
  - Press: United States: Associations: New York State Society of Newspaper Editors, 1955-1982 (Offsite-box 2183, Folder 16)
  - Press: United States: Associations: Newspaper Readership Council, 1977 (Offsite-box 2183, Folder 17)
  - Press: United States: Associations: Newswomen's Club of New York, 1941-1969 (Offsite-box 2183, Folder 18)
  - Press: United States: Associations: O, 1935-1986 (Offsite-box 2183, Folder 19)
  - Press: United States: Associations: Overseas Press Club, 1942-1992 (Offsite-box 2183, Folder 20-23)
  - Press: United States: Associations: P, 1939-1988 (Offsite-box 2183, Folder 24)
  - Press: United States: Associations: Publishers Association of New York City, 1953-1981 (Offsite-box 2183, Folder 25-30)
  - Press: United States: Associations: Q-S, 1953-1991 (Offsite-box 2183, Folder 31-33)
  - Press: United States: Associations: San Francisco Press Club, 1939-1980 (Offsite-box 2183, Folder 34)
  - Press: United States: Associations: Society of Magazine Writers, 1952-1975 (Offsite-box 2183, Folder 35)
  - Press: United States: Associations: Society of the Silurians, 1955-1992 (Offsite-box 2184, Folder 1)
  - Press: United States: Associations: Southern Newspaper Publishers Association, 1948-1991, undated (Offsite-box 2184, Folder 2)
  - Press: United States: Associations: Standing Committee of Correspondents, 1948-1989 (Offsite-box 2184, Folder 3)
  - Press: United States: Associations: State Department Correspondents Association, 1955-1980 (Offsite-box 2184, Folder 4)
  - Press: United States: Associations: T-W, 1934-1981 (Offsite-box 2184, Folder 5-8)
  - Press: United States: Associations: Washington Press Club, 1933-1985 (Offsite-box 2184, Folder 9-10)
  - Press: United States: Associations: White House Correspondents' Association, 1939-1993 (Offsite-box 2184, Folder 11)
  - Press: United States: Associations: Women in Communications, 1955-1982 (Offsite-box 2184, Folder 12)
  - Press: United States: Atlanta, 1958-1993 (Offsite-box 2184, Folder 13)
  - Press: United States: Atlanta, Ga., 1935-1988 (Offsite-box 2184, Folder 14-16)
  - Press: United States: Atlanta, Ga.: A-Z, 1939-1992 (Offsite-box 2184, Folder 17)
  - Press: United States: Atlanta, Ga.: Constitution, 1931-1992 (Offsite-box 2184, Folder 18-25)
  - Press: United States: Atlanta, Ga.: Georgian, 1939-1947 (Offsite-box 2184, Folder 26)
  - Press: United States: Atlanta, Ga.: Inquirer, 1961-1966 (Offsite-box 2184, Folder 27)
  - Press: United States: Atlanta, Ga.: Journal, 1935-1991 (Offsite-box 2184, Folder 28-34)
  - Press: United States: Atlanta, Ga.: Journal: Constitution, 1977-1992 (Offsite-box 2184, Folder 35)
  - Press: United States: Atlanta, Ga.: Times, 1964-1966 (Offsite-box 2184, Folder 36)
  - Press: United States: Atlanta, Ga.: World, 1932-1989 (Offsite-box 2184, Folder 37)
  - Press: United States: Atlantic City, N.J., 1955-1984 (Offsite-box 2184, Folder 38)
  - Press: United States: Atlantic Monthly, 1932-1992 (Offsite-box 2184, Folder 39-48)
  - Press: United States: Atlas, 1961-1974 (Offsite-box 2184, Folder 49)
  - Press: United States: Atlas World Press Review, 1974-1979, undated (Offsite-box 2184, Folder 50)
  - Press: United States: Audience, 1947-1993 (Offsite-box 2184, Folder 51)
  - Press: United States: Audience: Magazine, 1949-1993 (Offsite-box 2185, Folder 1-6)
  - Press: United States: Audience: Newspaper, 1947-1993 (Offsite-box 2185, Folder 7-10)
  - Press: United States: Augusta, Georgia, 1953-1992 (Offsite-box 2185, Folder 11)
  - Press: United States: Austin, Tex., 1975-1991 (Offsite-box 2185, Folder 12)
  - Press: United States: Austin, Tex.: American, 1958-1966 (Offsite-box 2185, Folder 13)
  - Press: United States: Austin, Tex.: American: Statesman, 1960-1984 (Offsite-box 2185, Folder 14)
  - Press: United States: Austin, Tex.: Statesman, 1958-1971 (Offsite-box 2185, Folder 15)
  - Press: United States: Austin, Tex.: Texas Observer, 1961-1986 (Offsite-box 2185, Folder 16)
  - Press: United States: Automobile Writers, 1963, 1971, 1990 (Offsite-box 2185, Folder 17)
  - Press: United States: Automotive News, 1938-1988 (Offsite-box 2185, Folder 18)
  - Press: United States: Auxilium Latinum, 1959-1960 (Offsite-box 2185, Folder 19)
  - Press: United States: Avant-Garde, 1967-1974 (Offsite-box 2185, Folder 20)
  - Press: United States: Ave Maria, 1954-1980 (Offsite-box 2185, Folder 21)
  - Press: United States: Avenue, 1978-1989 (Offsite-box 2185, Folder 22)
  - Press: United States: Aviation Daily, 1961-1991 (Offsite-box 2185, Folder 23)
  - Press: United States: Aviation Week and Space Technology, 1948-1993 (Offsite-box 2185, Folder 24-25)
  - Press: United States: Ba-Bi, 1931-1993, undated (Offsite-box 2185, Folder 26-30)
  - Press: United States: Bj-Business J, 1931-1993 (Offsite-box 2186, Folder 1-6)
  - Press: United States: Baltimore, Md., 1939-1992 (Offsite-box 2186, Folder 7)
  - Press: United States: Baltimore, Md.: A-Z, 1931-1992 (Offsite-box 2186, Folder 8)
  - Press: United States: Baltimore, Md.: "Afro-American" [African American], 1935-1992 (Offsite-box 2186, Folder 9)
  - Press: United States: Baltimore, Md.: News: American, 1964-1987 (Offsite-box 2186, Folder 10)
  - Press: United States: Baltimore, Md.: News: Post, 1948-1980 (Offsite-box 2186, Folder 11)
  - Press: United States: Baltimore, Md.: Sun, 1943, 1960-1993 (Offsite-box 2186, Folder 12-23)
  - Press: United States: Bangor, Me., 1954-1989 (Offsite-box 2186, Folder 24)
  - Press: United States: Bank Rate Monitor, 1983-1992 (Offsite-box 2186, Folder 25)
  - Press: United States: Baptist Standard, 1960-1963 (Offsite-box 2186, Folder 26)
  - Press: United States: Barron's, 1940-1992 (Offsite-box 2186, Folder 27)
  - Press: United States: Battle Line, 1960-1973 (Offsite-box 2186, Folder 28)
  - Press: United States: Bawl Street Journal, 1934-1970, undated (Offsite-box 2186, Folder 29)
  - Press: United States: Bay City, Mich., 1967 (Offsite-box 2186, Folder 30)
  - Press: United States: Berkeley, Calif., 1969-1993 (Offsite-box 2186, Folder 31)
  - Press: United States: Berkeley, Calif.: Barb, 1965-1981 (Offsite-box 2186, Folder 32)
  - Press: United States: Bettendorf, Iowa, 1956-1966 (Offsite-box 2186, Folder 33)
  - Press: United States: Better Farming, 1936-1956 (Offsite-box 2186, Folder 34)
  - Press: United States: Better Homes and Gardens, 1949-1993 (Offsite-box 2186, Folder 35)
  - Press: United States: Big Table, 1959 (Offsite-box 2186, Folder 36)
  - Press: United States: Bilingual and Multilingual, 1969-1989 (Offsite-box 2186, Folder 37)
  - Press: United States: Billboard, 1932-1992 (Offsite-box 2186, Folder 38-39)
  - Press: United States: Binghamton, N.Y., 1932-1981 (Offsite-box 2186, Folder 40)
  - Press: United States: Birmingham, Ala., 1935-1990 (Offsite-box 2186, Folder 41)
  - Press: United States: Birmingham, Ala.: News, 1935-1993 (Offsite-box 2187, Folder 1-5)
  - Press: United States: Black Enterprise, 1969-1993 (Offsite-box 2187, Folder 6)
  - Press: United States: Black Panther, 1968-1977 (Offsite-box 2187, Folder 7)
  - Press: United States: Black Scholar, 1970-1976 (Offsite-box 2187, Folder 8)
  - Press: United States: Black Sports, 1970-1971 (Offsite-box 2187, Folder 9)
  - Press: United States: Black World, 1970-1981 (Offsite-box 2187, Folder 10)
  - Press: United States: Blair and Ketchums County Journal, 1973-1975 (Offsite-box 2187, Folder 11)
  - Press: United States: Bloomington, Ill., 1939-1965 (Offsite-box 2187, Folder 12)
  - Press: United States: Blue Chip Economic Indicators, 1980-1993 (Offsite-box 2187, Folder 13)
  - Press: United States: Boise, Idaho, 1938-1980 (Offsite-box 2187, Folder 14)
  - Press: United States: Bon Appetit, 1975-1993 (Offsite-box 2187, Folder 15)
  - Press: United States: Book Digest, 1936, 1974-1982, undated (Offsite-box 2187, Folder 16)
  - Press: United States: Book World, 1967-1973 (Offsite-box 2187, Folder 17)
  - Press: United States: Boston, 1969-1991 (Offsite-box 2187, Folder 18)
  - Press: United States: Boston, Mass., 1935-1976, 1990 (Offsite-box 2187, Folder 19-21)
  - Press: United States: Boston, Mass.: A-Z, 1936-1993 (Offsite-box 2187, Folder 22-24)
  - Press: United States: Boston, Mass.: After Dark, 1971 (Offsite-box 2187, Folder 25)
  - Press: United States: Boston, Mass.: American, 1933-1971 (Offsite-box 2187, Folder 26)
  - Press: United States: Boston, Mass.: Christian Science Monitor, 1931-1993 (Offsite-box 2187, Folder 27-35)
  - Press: United States: Boston, Mass.: Globe, 1972-1993 (Offsite-box 2187, Folder 36-47)
  - Press: United States: Boston, Mass.: Globe, 1940-1971, undated (Offsite-box 2188, Folder 1-6)
  - Press: United States: Boston, Mass.: Herald, 1932-1966, 1982-1993 (Offsite-box 2188, Folder 7-13)
  - Press: United States: Boston, Mass.: Herald American, 1973-1987 (Offsite-box 2188, Folder 14-16)
  - Press: United States: Boston, Mass.: Herald-Traveler, 1933-1982 (Offsite-box 2188, Folder 17-18)
  - Press: United States: Boston, Mass.: Old Mole, 1969 (Offsite-box 2188, Folder 19)
  - Press: United States: Boston, Mass.: Pilot, 1935-1986 (Offsite-box 2188, Folder 20)
  - Press: United States: Boston, Mass.: Post, 1930-1985 (Offsite-box 2188, Folder 21-23)
  - Press: United States: Boston, Mass.: Record, 1932-1972 (Offsite-box 2188, Folder 24)
  - Press: United States: Boston, Mass.: Record-American, 1954-1983 (Offsite-box 2188, Folder 25)
  - Press: United States: Boston, Mass.: Record American and Herald Traveler, 1972 (Offsite-box 2188, Folder 26)
  - Press: United States: Boston, Mass.: Sunday Advertiser, 1935-1972 (Offsite-box 2188, Folder 27)
  - Press: United States: Boston, Mass.: Transcript, 1930-1941 (Offsite-box 2188, Folder 28)
  - Press: United States: Boston, Mass.: Traveler, 1963-1967 (Offsite-box 2188, Folder 29)
  - Press: United States: Boy's Life, 1961-1990, undated (Offsite-box 2188, Folder 30)
  - Press: United States: Bride's and Your New Home, 1959-1992 (Offsite-box 2188, Folder 31)
  - Press: United States: Bridgeport, Conn., 1938-1988 (Offsite-box 2188, Folder 32)
  - Press: United States: Broadcasting, 1961-1991 (Offsite-box 2188, Folder 33)
  - Press: United States: Broadside (Publication), 1964-1987 (Offsite-box 2188, Folder 34)
  - Press: United States: Broadsides (Subject), 1965-1979 (Offsite-box 2188, Folder 35)
  - Press: United States: Buffalo, N.Y., 1931-1982 (Offsite-box 2188, Folder 36)
  - Press: United States: Buffalo, N.Y.: Courier-Express, 1939-1983 (Offsite-box 2188, Folder 37)
  - Press: United States: Buffalo, N.Y.: News, 1936-1993, undated (Offsite-box 2188, Folder 38-41)
  - Press: United States: Buildings, 1968-1990 (Offsite-box 2188, Folder 42)
  - Press: United States: Bulletin of the Atomic Scientists, 1947-1992 (Offsite-box 2188, Folder 43)
  - Press: United States: Burlington, Vt., 1961-1989 (Offsite-box 2188, Folder 44)
  - Press: United States: Business Week, 1953-1993, undated (Offsite-box 2188, Folder 45-49)
  - Press: United States: Business Writers, 1936-1993 (Offsite-box 2188, Folder 50-51)
  - Press: United States: By-Lines, 1964-1989 (Offsite-box 2188, Folder 52)
  - Press: United States: Byte, 1977-1992 (Offsite-box 2189, Folder 1)
  - Press: United States: Caa-Conr, 1930-1993, undated (Offsite-box 2189, Folder 2-18)
  - Press: United States: Cons-Cz, 1931-1993 (Offsite-box 2190, Folder 1-7)
  - Press: United States: California, 1976-1993 (Offsite-box 2190, Folder 8)
  - Press: United States: Careers Today, 1959-1983 (Offsite-box 2190, Folder 9)
  - Press: United States: Catholic World, 1936-1965 (Offsite-box 2190, Folder 10)
  - Press: United States: Center, 1967-1986 (Offsite-box 2190, Folder 11)
  - Press: United States: Center Report, 1973 (Offsite-box 2190, Folder 12)
  - Press: United States: Charlotte, N.C., 1947-1967 (Offsite-box 2190, Folder 13)
  - Press: United States: Charlotte, N.C.: Caroline Israelite, 1957-1984 (Offsite-box 2190, Folder 14)
  - Press: United States: Charlotte, N.C.: News, 1955-1985 (Offsite-box 2190, Folder 15)
  - Press: United States: Charlotte, N.C.: Observer, 1932-1991 (Offsite-box 2190, Folder 16-21)
  - Press: United States: Charleston, S.C., 1932-1983 (Offsite-box 2190, Folder 22)
  - Press: United States: Charleston, W. Va., 1952-1987, undated (Offsite-box 2190, Folder 23)
  - Press: United States: Chattanooga, Tenn., 1936-1975, undated (Offsite-box 2190, Folder 24)
  - Press: United States: Chattanooga, Tenn.: News: Free Press, 1940-1986 (Offsite-box 2190, Folder 25)
  - Press: United States: Chattanooga, Tenn.: Post, 1966-1970 (Offsite-box 2190, Folder 26)
  - Press: United States: Chattanooga, Tenn.: Times, 1933-1992 (Offsite-box 2190, Folder 27)
  - Press: United States: Chemical Abstracts, 1958-1968 (Offsite-box 2190, Folder 28)
  - Press: United States: Chicago, Ill., 1937-1992, undated (Offsite-box 2190, Folder 29-34)
  - Press: United States: Chicago, Ill.: A-Z, 1931-1993, undated (Offsite-box 2190, Folder 35-42)
  - Press: United States: Chicago, Ill.: Bialian News, 1963-1978 (Offsite-box 2191, Folder 1)
  - Press: United States: Chicago, Ill.: Chicago's American, 1932-1969 (Offsite-box 2191, Folder 2-6)
  - Press: United States: Chicago, Ill.: Defender, 1938-1990 (Offsite-box 2191, Folder 7)
  - Press: United States: Chicago, Ill.: Herald and Examiner, 1930-1962, undated (Offsite-box 2191, Folder 8)
  - Press: United States: Chicago, Ill.: News, 1929-1981 (Offsite-box 2191, Folder 9-19)
  - Press: United States: Chicago, Ill.: Sun, 1941-1988 (Offsite-box 2191, Folder 20)
  - Press: United States: Chicago, Ill.: Sun-Times, 1948-1992, undated (Offsite-box 2191, Folder 21-41)
  - Press: United States: Chicago, Ill.: Times, 1929-1982 (Offsite-box 2191, Folder 42)
  - Press: United States: Chicago, Ill.: Today, 1969-1974 (Offsite-box 2191, Folder 43)
  - Press: United States: Chicago, Ill.: Tribune, 1973-1993 (Offsite-box 2191, Folder 44-60)
  - Press: United States: Chicago, Ill.: Tribune, 1930-1972 (Offsite-box 2192, Folder 1-14)
  - Press: United States: Chicago Journalism Review, 1968-1975 (Offsite-box 2192, Folder 15)
  - Press: United States: Chicago Reporter, 1974-1989 (Offsite-box 2192, Folder 16)
  - Press: United States: Children's Express, 1976-1980 (Offsite-box 2192, Folder 17)
  - Press: United States: Christian Advocate, 1926-1983 (Offsite-box 2192, Folder 18)
  - Press: United States: Christian Century, 1931-1991 (Offsite-box 2192, Folder 19-20)
  - Press: United States: Christian Herald, 1931-1977 (Offsite-box 2192, Folder 21)
  - Press: United States: Christianity and Crisis, 1941-1993 (Offsite-box 2192, Folder 22)
  - Press: United States: Christianity Today, 1930-1988 (Offsite-box 2192, Folder 23)
  - Press: United States: Chronicle of Higher Education, 1971-1993 (Offsite-box 2192, Folder 24)
  - Press: United States: Chronicle of Human Rights in the USSR, 1974-1984 (Offsite-box 2192, Folder 25)
  - Press: United States: Churchman, The, 1930-1974 (Offsite-box 2192, Folder 26)
  - Press: United States: Cincinnati, Ohio, 1932-1991 (Offsite-box 2192, Folder 27)
  - Press: United States: Cincinnati, Ohio: A-Z, 1931-1988 (Offsite-box 2192, Folder 28)
  - Press: United States: Cincinnati, Ohio: Enquirer, 1930-1991 (Offsite-box 2192, Folder 29-35)
  - Press: United States: Cincinnati, Ohio: Post, 1932-1979 (Offsite-box 2192, Folder 36)
  - Press: United States: Cincinnati, Ohio: Post and Times-Star, 1930-1973 (Offsite-box 2192, Folder 37)
  - Press: United States: Cincinnati, Ohio: Time-Star, 1940-1968 (Offsite-box 2192, Folder 38)
  - Press: United States: Cinema Reporters, 1954-1969 (Offsite-box 2192, Folder 39-40)
  - Press: United States: Circulation, 1991-1993 (Offsite-box 2192, Folder 41-43)
  - Press: United States: Circulation, 1931-1991 (Offsite-box 2193, Folder 1-27)
  - Press: United States: Circulation: Audit Bureau of Circulation, 1931-1991, undated (Offsite-box 2194, Folder 1)
  - Press: United States: City Hall Reporters, 1965-1989 (Offsite-box 2194, Folder 2)
  - Press: United States: Clarksburg, W. Va., 1953-1957 (Offsite-box 2194, Folder 3)
  - Press: United States: Cleveland, Ohio, 1933-1978, undated (Offsite-box 2194, Folder 4)
  - Press: United States: Cleveland, Ohio: A-Z, 1942-1987 (Offsite-box 2194, Folder 5)
  - Press: United States: Cleveland, Ohio: News, 1932-1966, undated (Offsite-box 2194, Folder 6)
  - Press: United States: Cleveland, Ohio: Plain Dealer, 1934-1993, undated (Offsite-box 2194, Folder 7-12)
  - Press: United States: Cleveland, Ohio: Press, 1934-1987 (Offsite-box 2194, Folder 13-18)
  - Press: United States: Co-Ed, 1955-1985 (Offsite-box 2194, Folder 19)
  - Press: United States: Collier's, 1929-1983 (Offsite-box 2194, Folder 20-22)
  - Press: United States: Colorado Springs, Colo., 1948-1986 (Offsite-box 2194, Folder 23)
  - Press: United States: Colorado Springs, Colo.: Free Press, 1955-1970 (Offsite-box 2194, Folder 24)
  - Press: United States: Columbia Journalism Review, 1961-1993 (Offsite-box 2194, Folder 25)
  - Press: United States: Columbia, S.C., 1950-1991 (Offsite-box 2194, Folder 26)
  - Press: United States: Columbus, Ga., 1935-1979 (Offsite-box 2194, Folder 27)
  - Press: United States: Columbus, Ohio, 1931-1968, 1981, undated (Offsite-box 2194, Folder 28)
  - Press: United States: Columbus, Ohio: A-Z, 1938, 1967, 1976 (Offsite-box 2194, Folder 29)
  - Press: United States: Columbus, Ohio: Citizen, 1937, 1959 (Offsite-box 2194, Folder 30)
  - Press: United States: Columbus, Ohio: Citizen-Journal, 1959-1986 (Offsite-box 2194, Folder 31)
  - Press: United States: Columbus, Ohio: Dispatch, 1938-1992 (Offsite-box 2194, Folder 32)
  - Press: United States: Columbus, Ohio: Ohio State Journal, 1938, 1959 (Offsite-box 2194, Folder 33)
  - Press: United States: Columnists, 1981-1993 (Offsite-box 2194, Folder 34-42)
  - Press: United States: Columnists, 1931-1980 (Offsite-box 2257, Folder 1-19)
  - Press: United States: Commentary, 1950-1993, undated (Offsite-box 2257, Folder 20-21)
  - Press: United States: Common Sense (Christian Education Association), 1971-1972 (Offsite-box 2257, Folder 22)
  - Press: United States: Common Sense (Hate Sheet), 1955-1963, undated (Offsite-box 2257, Folder 23)
  - Press: United States: Common Sense (Leftist Publication), 1932-1945 (Offsite-box 2257, Folder 24)
  - Press: United States: Common Sense (National Consumer Congress), 1974 (Offsite-box 2257, Folder 25)
  - Press: United States: Common Sense (People's Bicentennial Commission), 1975 (Offsite-box 2257, Folder 26)
  - Press: United States: Commonweal, 1930-1990 (Offsite-box 2257, Folder 27)
  - Press: United States: Competition, 1980-1993 (Offsite-box 2257, Folder 28-39)
  - Press: United States: Competition, 1964-1979 (Offsite-box 2258, Folder 1-7)
  - Press: United States: Conferences, 1955-1991 (Offsite-box 2258, Folder 8-9)
  - Press: United States: Confidential, 1954-1986, undated (Offsite-box 2258, Folder 10-15)
    Folder 11, which is supposed to contain materials from 1959, is empty.
  - Press: United States: Conservative Publications, 1955-1992 (Offsite-box 2258, Folder 16-19)
  - Press: United States: Consumer Bulletin, 1959 (Offsite-box 2258, Folder 20)
  - Press: United States: Consumer Reports, 1955-1992 (Offsite-box 2258, Folder 21-24)
  - Press: United States: Consumer Writers, 1969-1981 (Offsite-box 2258, Folder 25)
  - Press: United States: Contests, 1936-1993 (Offsite-box 2258, Folder 26-27)
  - Press: United States: Coronet, 1936-1973 (Offsite-box 2258, Folder 28)
  - Press: United States: Corpus Christi, Tex., undated (Offsite-box 2258, Folder 29)
  - Press: United States: Corpus Christi, Tex.: Caller, 1977-1979 (Offsite-box 2258, Folder 30)
  - Press: United States: Corpus Christi, Tex.: Caller-Times, 1970-1990 (Offsite-box 2258, Folder 31)
  - Press: United States: Corpus Christi, Tex.: Times, 1970 (Offsite-box 2258, Folder 32)
  - Press: United States: Cosmopolitan, 1930-1993 (Offsite-box 2258, Folder 33-34)
  - Press: United States: Counterspy, 1975-1981, undated (Offsite-box 2258, Folder 35)
  - Press: United States: Covert Action Information Bulletin, 1978-1982 (Offsite-box 2258, Folder 36)
  - Press: United States: Crusades, 1966-1992 (Offsite-box 2258, Folder 37-38)
  - Press: United States: Crusades, 1951-1965 (Offsite-box 2259, Folder 1-6)
  - Press: United States: Cry California, 1965-1970 (Offsite-box 2259, Folder 7)
  - Press: United States: Cue, 1938-1986 (Offsite-box 2259, Folder 8)
  - Press: United States: Cuero, Tex., 1955-1956, 1972 (Offsite-box 2259, Folder 9)
  - Press: United States: Daa-Dz, 1931-1993 (Offsite-box 2259, Folder 10-26)
  - Press: United States: Daedalus, 1961-1990 (Offsite-box 2259, Folder 27)
  - Press: United States: Dallas, Texas, 1935-1989 (Offsite-box 2259, Folder 28)
  - Press: United States: Dallas, Texas: A-Z, 1931-1993 (Offsite-box 2259, Folder 29-30)
  - Press: United States: Dallas, Texas: Express, 1967 (Offsite-box 2259, Folder 31)
  - Press: United States: Dallas, Texas: News, 1935-1991 (Offsite-box 2259, Folder 32-37)
  - Press: United States: Dallas, Texas: Times-Herald, 1937-1992 (Offsite-box 2259, Folder 38-41)
  - Press: United States: Dance, 1955-1993 (Offsite-box 2259, Folder 42)
  - Press: United States: Dayton, Ohio, 1931-1984 (Offsite-box 2260, Folder 1)
  - Press: United States: Dearborn, Mich., 1934-1971 (Offsite-box 2260, Folder 2)
  - Press: United States: Decision, 1941-1978 (Offsite-box 2260, Folder 3)
  - Press: United States: Deer Park, N.Y.: Suffolk Sun, 1966-1969 (Offsite-box 2260, Folder 4)
  - Press: United States: Deliveries, 1942-1992 (Offsite-box 2260, Folder 5-6)